[
    {   
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question":"'OS' computer abbreviation usually means ?",
        "answerOptions":["Order of Significance", "Open Software", "Operating System", "None of these"],
        "correctAnswers":["Operating System"],
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question":"Which of the following options is correct with regard to HTML?",
        "answerOptions":["It is a modelling language", "It is a scripting language", "It is a partial programming language", "It is used to structure documents"],
        "correctAnswers":["It is used to structure documents"],
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question":"How can you make a list that lists the items with numbers?",
        "answerOptions":["<ul>", "<list>", "<ol>", "<dl>"],
        "correctAnswers":["<ol>"],
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question":"All HTML comment tags are enclosed in what ?",
        "answerOptions":["<>", "<? and ?>", "# and #", "<!-- and -->"],
        "correctAnswers":["<!-- and -->"],
        "difficulty": 4
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "What type of framework is Next.js?",
        "answerOptions": ["Frontend", "Backend", "FullStack", "None of the above" ],
        "correctAnswers":["FullStack"],
        "difficulty": 5
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "Which tag is used to write the javascript code",
        "answerOptions": ["<script>", "<sp>", "<javascript>", "<java>"],
        "correctAnswers": ["<script>"],
        "difficulty": 6
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "_________ keyword is used to declare variables in javascript.",
        "answerOptions": ["var", "let", "Only A", "Only B"],
        "correctAnswers": ["var", "let"],
        "difficulty": 7
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript cannot do?",
        "answerOptions": ["JavaScript can react to events", "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements","JavaScript can be used to validate data","Javascript can give styles to the page"],
        "correctAnswers": ["JavaScript can react to events", "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements","JavaScript can be used to validate data"],
        "difficulty": 8
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Style?",
        "answerOptions": ["Linked", "Embedded", "Inline", "Orthogonal"],
        "correctAnswers": ["Orthogonal"],
        "difficulty": 9
    },
    {
        "quizName": "General Quiz",
        "question": "The elements <DIV> and <SPAN> have the following characteristics",
        "answerOptions": ["Element <DIV> inherits properties defined for <SPAN> in a stylesheet",
                        "Elements <SPAN> and <DIV> define content to be inline or block-level",
                        "<DIV> and <SPAN> are used as alternatives for the element <P>",
                        "<DIV> is used inside element <P>."],
        "correctAnswers": ["Elements <SPAN> and <DIV> define content to be inline or block-level"],
        "difficulty": 10
    }

]

